<resources>

    <string name="app_name">TourGuideApp</string>
    <string name="tab_sight">Sights</string>
    <string name="tab_new">What\'s on</string>
    <string name="tab_food">Food and drink</string>
    <string name="tab_shop">Shopping</string>
    <string name="email_subject">USE THIS APP TO FIND KEY ATTRACTIONS IN LONDON</string>
    <string name="email_data">mailto:developer@example.com</string>
    <string name="key_name">name</string>
    <string name="key_address">address</string>
    <string name="key_image">image</string>
    <string name="key_description">description</string>
    <string name="key_website">website</string>


    <!--- Sights strings details -->
    <string-array name="sights_name">
        <item>Tower Bridge</item>
        <item>Buckingham Palace</item>
        <item>London Eye</item>
        <item>Tate Modern</item>
        <item>Shakespeare\'s Globe Theatre</item>
        <item>Barbican</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="sights_description">
        <item>Tower Bridge is a combined bascule and suspension bridge in London
        built between 1886 and 1894. The bridge crosses the River Thames close to the Tower of London and has
        become an iconic symbol of London.</item>
        <item>Buckingham Palace is the London residence and administrative headquarters
        of the reigning monarch of the United Kingdom. Located in the City of Westminster, the palace is often at the
        centre of state occasions and royal hospitality.</item>
        <item>The London Eye is a giant Ferris wheel on the South Bank of the River Thames
        in London. Also known as the Millennium Wheel, it has also been called by its owners the British Airways London Eye,
        the Merlin Entertainments London Eye, the EDF Energy London Eye and, as of mid-January 2015, the Coca-Cola London Eye.</item>
        <item>Tate Modern is a modern art gallery located in London. It is Britain\'s national gallery of
        international modern art and forms part of the Tate group</item>
        <item>Shakespeare\'s Globe is the complex housing a reconstruction of the Globe Theatre,
        an Elizabethan playhouse associated with William Shakespeare, in the London Borough of Southwark, on the south bank of the River Thames.</item>
        <item>The Barbican Centre is a performing arts centre in the City of London and the largest of its kind in Europe.
        The Centre hosts classical and contemporary music concerts, theatre performances, film screenings and art exhibitions.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="sights_address">
        <item>Tower Bridge Rd, London SE1 2UP</item>
        <item>Westminster, London SW1A 1AA</item>
        <item>Lambeth, London SE1 7PB</item>
        <item>Bankside, London SE1 9TG</item>
        <item>21 New Globe Walk, London SE1 9DT</item>
        <item>Silk St, London EC2Y 8DS</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="sights_website">
        <item>http://www.towerbridge.org.uk/</item>
        <item>https://www.royalcollection.org.uk/visit/the-state-rooms-buckingham-palace</item>
        <item>https://www.londoneye.com/</item>
        <item>http://www.tate.org.uk/visit/tate-modern</item>
        <item>http://www.shakespearesglobe.com/</item>
        <item>http://www.barbican.org.uk/</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--- New events strings details -->
    <string-array name="new_name">
        <item>Luna Cinema </item>
        <item>Gigs at the Jazz Cafe</item>
        <item>Silent Disco at Cutty Sark</item>
        <item>Grayson Perry</item>
        <item>Greenwich Festival</item>
        <item>Tristan and Yseult</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="new_description">
        <item>The beauty of Luna Cinema is walking into a Royal Park or some
        other date-perfect location with a picnic just as everyone else is leaving. </item>
        <item>The Jazz Cafe is an award winning live music venue in Camden,
        known for its well known jazz, hip hop, soul and funk artists gracing its stage.</item>
        <item>Get ready to climb aboard the good ship Cutty Sark for Time Out\'s
        legendary silent disco. Have a nose around the world-famous attraction before donning a pair of headphones and dancing the night away.</item>
        <item>‘With great power comes great responsibility,’ said a wise uncle to
        his superhero nephew once. It\’s a sentiment that hovers around Grayson Perry\’s exhibition.</item>
        <item>From the cinematic waterfront setting of A View from the Bridge to exquisite
        South Korean choreography in a column of water and an exuberant techno parade in Woolwich, GDIF 2017 offers outdoor
        theatre adventures for everyone.</item>
        <item>Tristan and Yseult, the most successful and beloved of all of Kneehigh\’s shows,
        blends comedy, live music, grand passions and tender truths in an irresistible night of love.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="new_address">
        <item>1 Davies St, London W1K 3DB</item>
        <item>5 Parkway, Camden Town, London NW1 7PG</item>
        <item>King William Walk, London SE10 9HT</item>
        <item>32 London Bridge St, London SE1 9SG</item>
        <item>London SE10 8XJ</item>
        <item>Shakespeare Globe, South Bank</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="new_website">
        <item>http://www.thelunacinema.com</item>
        <item>http://www.thejazzcafelondon.com/</item>
        <item>http://www.visitgreenwich.org.uk/events/time-out-silent-disco-at-cutty-sark/</item>
        <item>http://www.serpentinegalleries.org/</item>
        <item>http://www.festival.org/festival/overview/15/2017/</item>
        <item>http://www.kneehigh.co.uk/</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--- Food places strings details -->
    <string-array name="food_name">
        <item>Greenwich Union</item>
        <item>Ryal Teas</item>
        <item>Jamie\'s Italian </item>
        <item>Zero Degrees</item>
        <item>Stick \'n\' Sushi</item>
        <item>Franco Manca</item>
        <item>BiBimBap</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="food_description">
        <item>Compact pub with flagstone floors that brews its own beers and also has an international food menu.</item>
        <item>Simple cafe for vegetarian breakfasts and lunches, tea, cakes and coffee beans ground to order.</item>
        <item>Celebrity chef\'s relaxed Italian chain, with rustic menu and antipasti bar.</item>
        <item>Fresh beer straight from the copper tanks plus wood-fired pizza and kilo pots of mussels.</item>
        <item>Japanese restaurant based on a renowned Danish concept, offering sushi and grilled yakitori skewers.</item>
        <item>Franco Manca is a sourdough pizza business with 36 pizzeria in London and southern England.</item>
        <item>Bibimbap, sometimes anglicized as bi bim bap or bi bim bop, is a Korean dish. The word literally means "mixed rice".</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="food_address">
        <item>56 Royal Hill, Greenwich, London SE10 8RT</item>
        <item>76 Royal Hill, Greenwich, London SE10 8RT</item>
        <item>17-,19 Nelson Rd, Greenwich, London SE10 9JB</item>
        <item>29-,31 Montpelier Vale, Lewisham, London SE3 0TJ</item>
        <item>11 Henrietta St, London WC2E 8PY</item>
        <item>51 Berwick St, Soho, London W1F 8SJ</item>
        <item>11 Greek St, Soho, London W1D 4DJ</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="food_website">
        <item>www.greenwichunion.com/</item>
        <item>https://www.royalteascafe.co.uk/</item>
        <item>https://www.jamieoliver.com/italian/restaurants/greenwich</item>
        <item>www.zerodegrees.co.uk</item>
        <item>http://www.sticksnsushi.co.uk/</item>
        <item>http://www.francomanca.co.uk</item>
        <item>www.bibimbapsoho.co.uk</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--- Shopping places strings details -->
    <string-array name="shop_name">
        <item>Victoria Place</item>
        <item>Westfield Stratford</item>
        <item>Angel</item>
        <item>Oxford Street</item>
        <item>Harrods</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="shop_description">
        <item>Shopping centre above station for clothing and gifts with a supermarket and fast-,food outlets.</item>
        <item>With a total retail floor area of 1,905,542 square feet, it is one of the largest urban shopping centres in Europe.</item>
        <item>Located off the ever-,hip Upper Street, Angel Central Shopping Centre (formerly known at The N1 Centre) has a vibrant and
        stylish collection of shops, cafes, restaurants, cinemas and music venues under its roof.</item>
        <item>Oxford Street is best known for Selfridges and the other big department
        stores which are all found in the section from Marble Arch to Oxford Circus, along with most of the big-,name multinationals.</item>
        <item>Harrods is a luxury department store located on Brompton Road in Knightsbridge, London. It is owned by the state of Qatar.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="shop_address">
        <item>115 Buckingham Palace Rd, London SW1W 9SJ</item>
        <item>Montfichet Rd, London E20 1EJ</item>
        <item>21 Parkfield St, London N1 0PS</item>
        <item>Oxford St, Soho, London W1B 3AG</item>
        <item>87-135 Brompton Rd, Knightsbridge, London SW1X 7XL</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="shop_website">
        <item>www.victoriaplace.co.uk/</item>
        <item>https://uk.westfield.com/stratfordcity</item>
        <item>www.angelcentral.co.uk/</item>
        <item>https://www.oxfordstreet.co.uk/shop/</item>
        <item>https://www.harrods.com/</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>